ĐỖ CÔNG HOÀNG DƯỢC SĨ



PERSONAL STATEMENT

I was born Bac Giang province in 1994. I was graduated from Ha Noi University of Pharmacy and became a pharmacist in June 2017.

I consider myself as not only an open and friendly but also active and hard-working person. I like making relationship and bringing happiness and

Although I do not have too much experience working as a Medical Representative but I am interested in this career and willing to be a professional sales staff.

Why don't we work together? I hope we can go futher to see I am the prospect staff that you need.

QUALITY

• Active and willing tolearn

other values in life to people.

- Careful, responsible andtrustworthy
- Able to work under pressure good at timemanagement
- Flexible and adaptable

Address:

42 Tran Cung Street, Co Nhue 1, Tu Liem, Ha Noi.

OBJECTIVE

- Take advantages of sales experience and knowdlege of Marketing to become a excellent sales staff, to gain our company's turnover
- Take all the opportunities to learn and developemy career with all my power and enthusiasm of youth
- Have my-owned Pharmacy company by the age of 45

SKILLS

SALES	••••••
TEAMWORK	*******
COMUNICATION	*******
PRESENTATATION	

LANGUAGE SKILL

• Basic English

OFFICE SOFWARES

• Good skill in office sofwares: Word, Powerpoint, Excell

EDUCATION

Graduated from *Hanoi University of Pharmacy* in 2017 **GPA**: 2,96 / 4,00.

Contact:

Phone:+84911475885

Email: doconghoang011@gmail.com

Facebook.com/do.hoang.564

WORK EXPERIENCE

From to June 2016 to March 2017

Introduce products, give advice and answer patient's inquiries about products

Pharmaceutical Corporation Green Valley

From to June 2017 to April 2018

Pharmaceutical representatives: Find output, extend the distribution channel functional foods.

Pharmaceutical Staff Truong Tho

From to April 2018 to August 2018

Experienced in Moderation Department

JSC Central Pharmaceutical I Pharbaco

OUTING ACTIVITIES



Champion the University's football league twice. As a member of VUG Hanoi University of Pharmacyteam.



3th Arward of the University's SV competition.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Fitness, Music
- Read book, news